Guide to the New York Building Congress Records WAG.167
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series VI: Photographs, 1936-2008
  - Suberies VI:A: Meetings, 1947-1999
    - Committee: Transportation, 1998 (Box 34, Folder 22)
    - Committee: Education, Dec 18, 1998 (Box 34, Folder 23)
    - Committee: Membership, Feb 13, 1998; Apr 2, 1998 (Box 34, Folder 24)
    - Committee: Public Buildings (Includes Patricia Lancaster), Jan 28, 1998 (Box 34, Folder 25)
    - Committee: Public Buildings, Sep 11, 1998 (Box 34, Folder 26)
    - Committee: Construction Controls, Dec 5, 1951 (Box 34, Folder 27)
    - Council of Presidents: Luncheon, Jun 22, 1983 (Box 34, Folder 28)
    - Council of Presidents: Arthur Levitt, Jr. (101 Club): Prints and Contact Sheets, May 20, 1987 (Box 34, Folder 29)
    - Council of Presidents: Stephen Berger (101 Club), Jun 6, 1987 (Box 34, Folder 30)
    - Council of Presidents (101 Club, Includes Andrew Stern), Sep 23, 1987 (Box 34, Folder 31)
    - Council of Presidents (101 Club, Includes Peter Vallone), Oct 21, 1987 (Box 34, Folder 32)
    - Council of Presidents (101 Club, Includes Sandy Fruchter), Dec 1987 (Box 34, Folder 33)
    - Council of Presidents (Includes Claire Shulman): Photos and Contact Sheets, Oct 19, 1988 (Box 34, Folder 34)
    - Council of Presidents (Grand Hyatt Hotel, Includes Ass. Marc Alan Siegel): Prints and Contact Sheets, Mar 15, 1989 (Box 34, Folder 35)
    - Council of Presidents: Luncheon: Contact Sheets, Jan 19, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 36)
    - Council of Presidents (Includes C. Wisbal): Prints and Negatives, [1994] (Box 34, Folder 37)
    - Council of Presidents: Breakfast Forum with Ruth Messinger: Prints and Negatives, 1995 (Box 34, Folder 38)
    - Council of Presidents: Breakfast Forum, 1995 (Box 34, Folder 39)
    - Council of Presidents: Breakfast Forum: Prints and Negatives, 1995 (Box 34, Folder 40)
    - Council of Presidents: Breakfast Forum with Robert Kiley, 1995 (Box 34, Folder 41)
    - Council of Presidents (Includes Luis Tormenta), Apr 17, 1996 (Box 34, Folder 42)
    - Council of Presidents (Includes Herman Berman): Prints and Negatives, Oct 16, 1996 (Box 34, Folder 43)
    - Council of Presidents (Includes Clay Lifflander), 1996 (Box 34, Folder 44)
    - Council of Presidents (Includes Fran Reiter), 1996 (Box 34, Folder 45)
    - Council of Presidents (Includes Frank Lombardi), Feb 19, 1997 (Box 34, Folder 46)
    - Council of Presidents (Includes Harry Spencer), Apr 15, 1997 (Box 34, Folder 47)
    - Council of Presidents, Oct 15, 1997 (Box 34, Folder 48)
    - [Council of Presidents]: Breakfast Forum (Includes Robert Catell), Nov 13, 1997 (Box 34, Folder 49)
    - Council of Presidents (Includes Cathy Nolan): Prints and Negatives, Nov 13, 1997-Nov 19, 1997 (Box 34, Folder 50)
    - Council of Presidents (Includes Colonel Gary Thomas), Dec 17, 1997 (Box 34, Folder 51)
    - Council of Presidents: Reception, 1997 (Box 34, Folder 52)
    - Council of Presidents: Breakfast Forum (Includes Mark Green and Frederick Ferrer): Prints and Negatives, 1997 (Box 34, Folder 53)
    - Council of Presidents (Includes Brad Race): Prints and Negatives, Mar 20, 1998 (Box 34, Folder 54)
    - Council of Presidents (Includes Joseph Lynch), Apr 15, 1998 (Box 34, Folder 55)
    - Council of Presidents (Includes Kathy Coylde): Prints and Negatives, 1998 (Box 34, Folder 56)
    - Council of Presidents: Breakfast Forum (Includes Carl McCall), May 1998 (Box 34, Folder 57)
    - Council of Presidents (Includes Deborah Wright), Feb 18, 1999 (Box 34, Folder 58)
    - Council of Presidents (Includes Robert King), Feb 25, 1999 (Box 34, Folder 59)
    - Council of Presidents: Prints and Negatives, Sep 20, 2000 (Box 34, Folder 60)
    - Council of Presidents: Prints and Negatives, Oct 18, 2000 (Box 34, Folder 61)
    - Council of Presidents, undated (Box 34, Folder 62)
    - Formal Acceptance of Wage Stabilization Agreement (Office of the Building Trades Employers' Association), Mar 24, 1948 (Box 34, Folder 63)
    - Public Agency Council [on Transportation]: Prints and Negatives, 1996 (Box 34, Folder 64)
    - Public Agency Council: Capital Needs, undated (Box 34, Folder 65)
    - Public Agency Council, 1999 (Box 34, Folder 66)
    - Staff, Council of Presidents and Economic Development Committee (Includes Robert Boyle), 1997 (Box 34, Folder 67)
    - Unidentified Meeting (Hotel Baltimore), Oct 16, 1950 (Box 34, Folder 68)
    - Unidentified Meeting, Sep 29, 1955 (Box 34, Folder 69)
    - Unidentified Meeting, Jul 2, 1969 (Box 34, Folder 70)
    - Unidentified Meeting, Sep 1976 (Box 34, Folder 71)
    - Unidentified Meetings, undated (Box 34, Folder 72)
    - Unidentified NY Delegation to Washginton D.C., Feb 10, 1947 (Box 34, Folder 73)
    - Unidentified Presentation, undated (Box 34, Folder 74)
  - Subseries VI:B: Events, 1944-2008
    - Anniversary Dinner (40th, Hotel Astor): Includes Richard A. Wolff, S.F. Voorhees, John Lowry, James Foley, John F. Hennesey, C. George Dandrow, Alan Horowitz, and Bradford N. Clark, Oct 5, 1961 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Anniversary (50th), Mar 28, 1971-Mar 31, 1971 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Anniversary (50th): Conference, Mar 29, 1971- Mar 31, 1971 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Anniversary (60th), Mar 19, 1982 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Anniversary (65th): Luncheon (Includes Alfonse D'Amato): Prints and Contact Sheets, May 19, 1986 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Anniversary (76th): Leadership Awards Luncheon (1), 1997 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Anniversary (76th): Leadership Awards Luncheon (2), 1997 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Anniversary (76th): Leadership Awards Luncheon (3), 1997 (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Anniversary (76th): Leadership Awards Luncheon (4), 1997 (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Anniversary (77th): Leadership Awards Luncheon (1), 1998 (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - Anniversary (77th): Leadership Awards Luncheon (2), 1998 (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - Anniversary (77th): Luncheon Committee Kick-Off Reception: Prints and Negatives, [1998] (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - Anniversary (78th): Leadership Awards Luncheon (1), May 12, 1999 (Box 35, Folder 13)
    - Anniversary (78th): Leadership Awards Luncheon (2), May 12, 1999 (Box 35, Folder 14)
    - Anniversary (78th): Leadership Awards Luncheon (3), May 12, 1999 (Box 35, Folder 15)
    - Anniversary (78th): Leadership Awards Luncheon (4), May 12, 1999 (Box 35, Folder 16)
    - Anniversary (78th): Leadership Awards Luncheon (5), May 12, 1999 (Box 35, Folder 17)
    - Anniversary (79th): Leadership Awards Luncheon, May 4, 2000 (Box 35, Folder 18)
    - Breakfast Forum (Includes Larry Reuter), Apr 19, 1996 (Box 35, Folder 19)
    - Breakfast Forum (Includes Sheldon Silver), Feb 27, 1997 (Box 35, Folder 20)
    - Breakfast Forum (Alan Hevesi): Prints and Negatives, Jun 1997 (Box 35, Folder 21)
    - Breakfast Forum (Includes John L. Bruno): Prints and Negatives, Dec 18, 1997 (Box 35, Folder 22)
    - Breakfast Forum (Includes Joel Miele), 1997 (Box 35, Folder 23)
    - Breakfast Forum (Includes Larry Reuter), 1997 (Box 35, Folder 24)
    - Breakfast Forum (Includes Joseph Boardman), Feb 19, 1998 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Breakfast Forum (Includes Luis Tormenta), Mar 19, 1998 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Breakfast Forum (EDC): Prints and Negatives, Feb 23, 1999 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Breakfast Forum (Includes Rudy Crew), Mar 19, 1999 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Breakfast Forum (Includes Iris Weinshall): Prints and Negatives, Mar 29, 2001 (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - [Breakfast?] Forum, undated (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Brooklyn Sports Foundation Auction, May 2000 - Jun 2000 (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - Building Code: Press Conference, Feb 6, 1961 (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - Building Code (1963): Signing (Includes Harold Birm, Charles E. Schaffner and Peter Reidy) (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - Building Code: Press Conference, 1967 (Box 36, Folder 10)
    - Building Code: Signing, Nov 6, 1968 (Box 36, Folder 11)
    - Business / Labor Breakfast (Sheraton Center, Includes A.L. Delli Bovi), Jan 12, 1989 (Box 36, Folder 12)
    - City Council: Breakfast: Prints and Negatives, Apr 28, 1998 (Box 36, Folder 13)
    - City Council: Reception, Apr 1998 (Box 36, Folder 14)
    - Clark, Bradford: Swearing in as Department of Public Works Commissioner, Oct 13, 1963 (Box 36, Folder 15)
    - Coletti, Louis J.: Testifying before the U.S. House Subcommittee on Health and the Environment, Aug 3, 1987 (Box 36, Folder 16)
    - C.I.B.D. [Construction Industry Development Board] Summit, 1996 (Box 36, Folder 17)
    - Co-op Holiday Party, 1997 (Box 36, Folder 18)
    - Dinner: Max Foley Jubilee, May 10, 1949 (Box 36, Folder 19)
    - Dinner (Unidentified): Negatives, Jun 1959 (?) (Box 36, Folder 20)
    - [Dinner]: Curtain Call, Dec 1959 (Box 36, Folder 21)
    - Dinner: Kick-Off Reception, Sep 1998 (Box 36, Folder 22)
    - [Dinner: Event with Speakers] (1), undated (Box 36, Folder 23)
    - [Dinner: Event with Speakers] (2), undated (Box 36, Folder 24)
    - Floyd, William: Farewell Party, 1996 (Box 36, Folder 25)
    - Fun and Frolic, Dec 18, 1944 (Box 36, Folder 26)
    - Fun and Frolic, Dec 18, 1945 (Box 36, Folder 27)
    - Fun and Frolic, Dec 19, 1946 (Box 36, Folder 28)
    - Fun and Frolic, Dec 18, 1947 (Box 36, Folder 29)
    - Fun and Frolic, Dec 21, 1948 (Box 36, Folder 30)
    - Fun and Frolic, Dec 20, 1949 (Box 36, Folder 31)
    - Fun and Frolic, Dec 19, 1950 (Box 36, Folder 32)
    - Fun and Frolic: Rehearsal, Dec 17, 1951 (Box 36, Folder 33)
    - Fun and Frolic, Dec 18, 1951 (Box 36, Folder 34)
    - Fun and Frolic, Dec 18, 1952 (Box 36, Folder 35)
    - Fun and Frolic, Dec 22, 1953 (Box 36, Folder 36)
    - Fun and Frolic, Dec 21, 1954 (Box 36, Folder 37)
    - Fun and Frolic, Dec 20, 1955 (Box 36, Folder 38)
    - Fun and Frolic, Dec 18, 1956 (Box 36, Folder 39)
    - Fun and Frolic, Dec 17, 1957 (Box 36, Folder 40)
    - Fun and Frolic, 1958 (Box 36, Folder 41)
    - Fun and Frolic (1), Dec 15, 1959 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Fun and Frolic (2), Dec 15, 1959 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Fun and Frolic (3), Dec 15, 1959 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Fun and Frolic, 1960 (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - Fun and Frolic, [1961?] (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - Fun and Frolic (1), Dec 18, 1962 (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Fun and Frolic (2), Dec 18, 1962 (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - Fun and Frolic (3), Dec 18, 1962 (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - Fun and Frolic (1), Dec 17, 1963 (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - Fun and Frolic (2), Dec 17, 1963 (Box 37, Folder 10)
    - Fun and Frolic, Dec 15, 1964 (Box 37, Folder 11)
    - Fun and Frolic, Dec 14, 1965 (Box 37, Folder 12)
    - Fun and Frolic (1), Dec 21, 1966 (Box 37, Folder 13)
    - Fun and Frolic (2), Dec 21, 1966 (Box 37, Folder 14)
    - Fun and Frolic (2), Dec 21, 1966 (Box 37, Folder 14)
    - Fun and Frolic (1), Dec 13, 1967 (Box 37, Folder 15)
    - Fun and Frolic (2), Dec 13, 1967 (Box 37, Folder 16)
    - Fun and Frolic (1), Dec 11, 1968 (Box 37, Folder 17)
    - Fun and Frolic (2), Dec 11, 1968 (Box 37, Folder 18)
    - Fun and Frolic (1), Dec 18, 1969 (Box 37, Folder 19)
    - Fun and Frolic (2), Dec 18, 1969 (Box 37, Folder 20)
    - Fun and Frolic, Dec 17, 1970 (Box 37, Folder 21)
    - Fun and Frolic: Prints and Contact Sheets, Dec 16, 1971 (Box 37, Folder 22)
    - Fun and Frolic, 1972 (Box 37, Folder 23)
    - Fun and Frolic (1), Dec 13, 1973 (Box 37, Folder 24)
    - Fun and Frolic (2): Prints and Contact Sheets, Dec 13, 1973 (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Fun and Frolic, Dec 16, 1974 (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Fun and Frolic (1), Dec 17, 1975 (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - Fun and Frolic (2), Dec 17, 1975 (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - Fun and Frolic, Dec 15, 1976 (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - Fun and Frolic, Dec 14, 1977 (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - Fun and Frolic, Dec 13, 1978 (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - Fun and Frolic, Dec 12, 1979 (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - Fun and Frolic, Dec 17, 1980 (Box 38, Folder 9)
    - Fun and Frolic, Dec 17, 1980 (Box 38, Folder 10)
    - Fun and Frolic, 1981 (Box 38, Folder 11)
    - Fun and Frolic (1), Dec 15, 1982 (Box 38, Folder 12)
    - Fun and Frolic (2), Dec 15, 1982 (Box 38, Folder 13)
    - Fun and Frolic (3): Prints and Contact Sheets, Dec 15, 1982 (Box 38, Folder 14)
    - Fun and Frolic (1), Dec 14, 1983 (Box 38, Folder 15)
    - Fun and Frolic (2): Prints and Contact Sheets, Dec 14, 1983 (Box 38, Folder 16)
    - Fun and Frolic, Dec 18, 1984 (Box 38, Folder 17)
    - Fun and Frolic, Dec 17, 1986 (Box 38, Folder 18)
    - Fun and Frolic: Prints and Contact Sheets (1), Dec 17, 1986 (Box 38, Folder 19)
    - Fun and Frolic: Prints and Contact Sheets (2), Dec 17, 1986 (Box 38, Folder 20)
    - Fun and Frolic, Dec 16, 1987 (Box 38, Folder 21)
    - Fun and Frolic (1), undated (Box 38, Folder 22)
    - Fun and Frolic (2), undated (Box 38, Folder 23)
    - Fun and Frolic: Negatives and Contact Sheets, undated (Box 38, Folder 24)
    - General Events (Identified), 1947-1972, undated (Box 38, Folder 25)
    - Ginsburg, Pam: Birthday Event, Mar 31, 1998 (Box 38, Folder 26)
    - Guggenheim Museum Event, Aug 2000 (Box 38, Folder 27)
    - Hennessy, John: Party, Aug 20, 1958 (Box 38, Folder 28)
    - Hevesi, Alan: Event: Prints and Negatives, Oct 1998 (Box 38, Folder 29)
    - Holiday Party, 1996 (Box 38, Folder 30)
    - Holiday Show Entertainment: The Capital Steps (Grand Hyatt Hotel), Dec 20, 1988 (Box 38, Folder 31)
    - Howard J. Rubenstein Assoc., "Rebuilding New York": Contact Sheets, Oct 13, 1987 (Box 38, Folder 32)
    - Industry Recognition Dinner (Grand Hyatt Hotel), Oct 29, 1996 (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Industry Recognition Dinner Kick-Off: Prints and Negatives, Sep 1997 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Industry Recognition Dinner (1), Oct 30, 1997 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Industry Recognition Dinner (2), Oct 30, 1997 (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Industry Recognition Dinner (3), Oct 30, 1997 (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Industry Recognition Dinner (4), Oct 30, 1997 (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - Industry Recognition Dinner (5), Oct 30, 1997 (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - Industry Recognition Dinner (6), Oct 30, 1997 (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - Industry Recognition Dinner (7), Oct 30, 1997 (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - Industry Recognition Dinner (8), Oct 30, 1997 (Box 39, Folder 10)
    - Industry Recognition Dinner (1), 1998 (Box 39, Folder 11)
    - Industry Recognition Dinner (2), 1998 (Box 39, Folder 12)
    - Industry Recognition Dinner (3), 1998 (Box 39, Folder 13)
    - Industry Recognition Dinner (4), 1998 (Box 39, Folder 14)
    - Industry Recognition Dinner (5), 1998 (Box 39, Folder 15)
    - Industry Recognition Dinner (6), 1998 (Box 39, Folder 16)
    - Industry Recognition Dinner (7), 1998 (Box 39, Folder 17)
    - Industry Recognition Dinner (8), 1998 (Box 39, Folder 18)
    - Industry Recognition Dinner: Kick-Off (Beacon Restaurant): Prints and Negatives, Sep 9, 1999 (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - Industry Recognition Dinner: Kick-Off Reception: Prints and Negatives, Sep 2000 (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - John F. Kennedy International Airport Redevelopment: Slide, Dec 1997 (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Luncheon, May 21, 1952 (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - Luncheon: NYBC and American Institute of Architects, Jun 26, 1952 (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - Luncheon: Annual, May 5, 1958 (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - Luncheon: Gillroy Testimonial, Nov 10, 1958 (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - Luncheon: New Members, Nov 17, 1958 (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - Luncheon: Annual (Hotel Commodore, Includes George Meany): Prints and Contact Sheets, Apr 27, 1967 (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - Luncheon: John V. Lindsay, Oct 10, 1972 (Box 40, Folder 10)
    - Luncheon: Unidentified, 1977 (Box 40, Folder 11)
    - Luncheon: Contact Sheets, May 11, 1978 (Box 40, Folder 12)
    - Luncheon: Prints and Contact Sheets, Oct 27, 1978 (Box 40, Folder 13)
    - Luncheon: Ed Koch, Sep 27, 1983 (Box 40, Folder 14)
    - Luncheon: Annual: Gerald Ford, Apr 4, 1984 (Box 40, Folder 15)
    - Luncheon: Ed Koch: Prints and Contact Sheets, Oct 6, 1986 (Box 40, Folder 16)
    - Luncheon: Senator Daniel P. Moynihan, Sep 14, 1987 (Box 40, Folder 17)
    - Luncheon: First Leadership Awards (Includes Edward Koch, Arthur Levitt, Jr., and Robert Wagner, Jr.): Prints and Contact Sheets, Mar 29, 1988 (Box 40, Folder 18)
    - Luncheon: Richard Ravich: Prints and Contact Sheets, Oct 21, 1988 (Box 40, Folder 19)
    - Luncheon: Leadership Awards: Prints and Contact Sheets, Mar 28, 1989 (Box 40, Folder 20)
    - Luncheon: Leadership Awards: Prints and Negatives, 1996 (Box 40, Folder 21)
    - Luncheon: Millard, Oct 16, 1997 (Box 40, Folder 22)
    - Luncheon: Guy Molinari, 1997 (Box 40, Folder 23)
    - Luncheon: Gargano, Apr 23, 1998 (Box 40, Folder 24)
    - Luncheon: Gargano: Prints and Negatives, Apr 23, 1998 (Box 40, Folder 25)
    - Luncheon: Transportation: Prints and Negatives, Jun 1999 (Box 40, Folder 26)
    - Luncheon Committee Kick-Off, 1999 (Box 40, Folder 27)
    - Luncheon: "T and I", 2000 (Box 40, Folder 28)
    - Luncheon and Press Conference: Energy Report, Jan 25, 2001 (Box 40, Folder 29)
    - Luncheon: Kick-Off Reception (Grand Havana Hotel), undated (Box 40, Folder 30)
    - Mayoral Meeting (?): Prints, Contact Sheet and Negatives, Nov 10, 1976(?) (Box 40, Folder 31)
    - Membership Appreciation Event: Negatives, 1998 (Box 40, Folder 32)
    - NYBC Construction Forecast Seminar (McGraw Hill Building), Nov 1987 (Box 40, Folder 33)
    - NYBC - MIA [Marble Institute of America]: Five Year Plan, undated (Box 40, Folder 34)
    - NYBC Update, Nov 6, 1992 (Box 40, Folder 35)
    - New Member Cocktail Party, Nov 17, 1958 (Box 40, Folder 36)
    - New York Association of Realty Managers Event: Prints and Negatives, undated (Box 40, Folder 37)
    - Officers Retirement Party, Sep 26, 1972 (Box 40, Folder 38)
    - Outing (Westchester Country Club), Jun 26, 1945 (Box 40, Folder 39)
    - Outing (North Hills Country Club), Jun 18, 1946 (Box 40, Folder 40)
    - Outing (North Hills Country Club), Jun 26, 1947 (Box 40, Folder 41)
    - Outing (North Hills Country Club), Jun 1948 (Box 40, Folder 42)
    - Outing (North Hills Country Club), Jun 23, 1949 (Box 40, Folder 43)
    - Outing (North Hills Country Club), Jun 22, 1950 (Box 40, Folder 44)
    - Outing (North Hills Country Club), Jun 22, 1950 (Box 40, Folder 45)
    - Outing (N.H.S.C.) (1), Jun 21, 1951 (Box 40, Folder 46)
    - Outing (N.H.S.C.) (2), Jun 21, 1951 (Box 40, Folder 47)
    - Outing: Outing Committee, 1951 (Box 40, Folder 48)
    - Outing (Westchester Country Club) (1), Jun 16, 1952 (Box 40, Folder 49)
    - Outing (Westchester Country Club) (2), Jun 16, 1952 (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - Outing (Westchester Country Club) (3), Jun 16, 1952 (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - Outing, 1953 (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - Outing (Westchester Country Club), Jun 14, 1954 (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - Outing (Westchester Country Club), Jun 13, 1955 (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - Outing (Westchester Country Club), Jun 11, 1956 (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - Outing, Jun 10, 1957 (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - Outing (Westchester Country Club), Jun 9, 1958 (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - Outing, Jun 15, 1959 (Box 41, Folder 9)
    - Outing: Outing Committee, Oct 1959 (Box 41, Folder 10)
    - Outing, Jun 1960 (Box 41, Folder 11)
    - Outing (Westchester Country Club), Jun 13, 1961 (Box 41, Folder 12)
    - Outing (Westchester Country Club), Jun 10, 1962 (Box 41, Folder 13)
    - Outing (Westchester Country Club), Jun 10, 1963 (Box 41, Folder 14)
    - Outing: Outing Committee, Sep 1963 (Box 41, Folder 15)
    - Outing, Jun 22, 1964 (Box 41, Folder 16)
    - Outing, Jun 28, 1965 (Box 41, Folder 17)
    - Outing, Jun 13, 1966 (Box 41, Folder 18)
    - Outing (Westchester Country Club), Jun 12, 1967 (Box 41, Folder 19)
    - Outing (Westchester Country Club), Jun 10, 1968 (Box 41, Folder 20)
    - Outing (Westchester Country Club), Jun 9, 1969 (Box 41, Folder 21)
    - Outing (Westchester Country Club), Jun 8, 1970 (Box 41, Folder 22)
    - Outing (Westchester Country Club), Jun 7, 1971 (Box 41, Folder 23)
    - Outing (Westchester Country Club), 1972 (Box 41, Folder 24)
    - Outing: Prints and Contact Sheets, Jun 1973 (Box 41, Folder 25)
    - Outing, Jun 1974 (Box 41, Folder 26)
    - [Outing], circa 1976? (Box 41, Folder 27)
    - Outing, Jun 16, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 28)
    - [Outing], Jun 15, 1981 (Box 41, Folder 29)
    - Outing: Prints and Contact Sheets, Jun 28, 1982 (Box 41, Folder 30)
    - Outing: Prints and Contact Sheets, Jun 18, 1983 or Jun 27, 1983 (Box 41, Folder 31)
    - Outing: Contact Sheets, Jun 18, 1984 (Box 41, Folder 32)
    - Outing (1), 1985 (Box 41, Folder 33)
    - Outing (2), 1985 (Box 41, Folder 34)
    - Outing: Contact Sheets, Jun 29, 1987 (Box 41, Folder 35)
    - Outing: Prints and Negatives, Jun 13, 1988 (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - Outing, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Outing, 1995 (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - Outing, 1996 (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - Outing, 1997 (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - Outing, 1998 (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - Outing, 1999 (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - Outing 1, undated (Box 42, Folder 8)
    - Outing 2, undated (Box 42, Folder 9)
    - Outing 3, undated (Box 42, Folder 10)
    - Outing 4, undated (Box 42, Folder 11)
    - Outings, 1969, undated (Box 42, Folder 12)
    - Peter's Place Rededication Event: Prints and Negatives, May 24, 2000 (Box 42, Folder 13)
    - Presentation of Plaque to John Klenke: Prints and Negatives, May 25, 1960 (Box 42, Folder 14)
    - P.W.C. Awards, Mar 16, 2000 (Box 42, Folder 15)
    - Reception: Peter J. Brennan, Dec 18, 1972 (Box 42, Folder 16)
    - Reception: George Fox Retirement, Sep 15, 1987 (Box 42, Folder 17)
    - Reception: Holiday: Prints and Negatives, Dec 1996 (Box 42, Folder 18)
    - Reception: State Legislature, 1996 (Box 42, Folder 19)
    - Reception: Membership Appreciation: Prints and Negatives, Sep 30, 1997 (Box 42, Folder 20)
    - Reception: Membership Appreciation, 1998 (Box 42, Folder 21)
    - Reception: Membership Appreciation (1), Nov 4, 1999 (Box 42, Folder 22)
    - Reception: Membership Appreciation (2), Nov 4, 1999 (Box 42, Folder 23)
    - Reception: C.B.B.D., Sep 24, 2000 (Box 42, Folder 24)
    - Reception: Membership Appreciation, Sep 2000 (Box 42, Folder 25)
    - Skidmore Birthday Party, Oct 16, 1950 (Box 42, Folder 26)
    - Skidmore Birthday Party (Hotel Baltimore), Apr 8, 1952 (Box 42, Folder 27)
    - Spitzer, Elliot: Event, circa 2008 (Box 42, Folder 28)
    - Staff [Event], circa 1999 (Box 42, Folder 29)
    - Surprise Party: Board of Governors Celebration of Past Presidents, Sep 29, 1955 (Box 42, Folder 30)
    - Times Square Event, [1998] (Box 42, Folder 31)
    - Transportation Event with [Port Authority], Apr 1, 1996 (Box 42, Folder 32)
    - Tunnel Tour, Jan 9, 1973 (Box 42, Folder 33)
    - Unidentified [Awards] Event, undated (Box 42, Folder 34)
    - Unidentified Event, Apr 8, 1963 (Box 42, Folder 35)
    - Unidentified Event, Jan 2000 (Box 42, Folder 36)
    - Unidentified Event: Prints and Negatives, Feb 27, 2001 (Box 42, Folder 37)
    - Unidentified Event 1 (1), undated (Box 42, Folder 38)
    - Unidentified Event 1 (2), undated (Box 42, Folder 39)
    - Unidentified Event 2 (1), undated (Box 42, Folder 40)
    - Unidentified Event 2 (2), undated (Box 42, Folder 41)
    - Unidentified Event 3, undated (Box 42, Folder 42)
    - Unidentified Event 4, undated (Box 42, Folder 43)
    - Unidentified Event 5, undated (Box 42, Folder 44)
    - Unidentified Event 6 (Includes Claire Shulman), undated (Box 42, Folder 45)
    - Unidentified Event 7: Negatives, undated (Box 42, Folder 46)
    - Unidentified Event [Leadership Awards Luncheon?], undated (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - Unidentified Event [Leadership Awards Luncheon?], undated (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - Unidentified Event and Presentation 1: Prints and Contact Sheets, undated (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - Unidentified Event and Presentation 2, undated (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - Unidentified Event and Presentation 3, undated (Box 43, Folder 5)